{
    "id": "f4c97a003d7e479494ac40c46d146cee",
    "title": "Omission Of That",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I knew ………………………. didn’t want to help me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "that she",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7eee70ef957845c5bd18488cd475639a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie said ………………….. was feeling better.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "that she",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "609fefd014784e488881592b37330d09"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. should forget me so quickly was rather a shock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "That she",
                "She",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "62a9cb5c35f94d1eb484103161d5d54f"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. she was a minor made it difficult for her to get a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The fact",
                "The fact that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "829336a2d6724a6d99f38aff2230a748"
        },
        {
            "question": "James replied ……………………….. was doing fine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "that he",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "47ede634c246453887c9c712ebcbbdbf"
        },
        {
            "question": "He shouted ………………………… was busy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "that he",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2c15203985084a7eac62835e5e1e283c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many people had disagreed with the Copernicus’ view ……………………… revolved round the sun.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the earth",
                "that the earth",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f6b5a3f30cd45e8bb81966695854496"
        },
        {
            "question": "I thought …………………. were in Singapore.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "that you",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dfd747bf347e47dc824b6eeb53a17e97"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was surprised ………………….. didn’t come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "that she",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4aae7b14f8f04a0eab65958cca4d91a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spoke in a low voice so ………………………. wouldn’t wake up the baby.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "that he",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8256e001eee344a6ac7818ae4015ce22"
        }
    ]
}